we'll start recording here.
All right,
So now I have to remember where we left off last week.
We're talking.
Don't worry.
We had gotten to,
um we had gotten to the point where we're starting to talk about,
um,
about your children.
He talked a little bit about where you grew up,
and then the point in your life where you were starting to have children.
Many you mentioned that you had?
No.
If you had three of them at the time,
and then another one came a little bit later.
So no,
if you want.
If that's where you want.
Pick back up.
Just Are you okay?
So,
no.
In the fall
on,
then my older a boy was born in number.
Okay?
And then we have to make it through the winter with
really,
really cold winter.
He did all right.
I have my dad like,
Grandad were so excited because the other boy
so But we did all right.
And then the second year,
we I think it was toward the end of the second year
way build a house and moved in our
trailer.
I have no idea what happened to the trail.
Let any way way we moved into this house.
It was a one bedroom,
too upstairs in a full basement,
which was made into apartment with three.
We read it,
but it was it was for the party.
The only problem was with it Waas that
the,
uh,
basement and the sewer system when building guns
was probably around the turn of the century.
Okay.
And it was what they call open.
Okay,
so the water table get above the store,
this tour and don't work.
Okay.
So what happened,
Frank?
Because snow would melt.
Yeah,
allow that.
At that point,
you got a real problem.
What?
And it was a a lot.
They're nothing like d'oh.
Except replace the whole sources,
right?
Sure,
they probably have you done yet
date away?
We,
uh,
turned out rather well.
Oh,
yeah,
I brought the welding
menus or trucks where
no gas
actually like Oh,
you right.
We call it fake.
Here we go.
Elfi Gas trucks.
You this?
So they want to sell a building.
And I bought that thing,
Moved it down there on the back.
It was a late late will.
Eventually,
I waded into job into a business
way.
Had all of repair business.
But anyway,
there was kind of the venture with that because I went up to
did major building.
They told me with.
So then I made a foundation,
poured concrete,
did that.
So yeah,
the we're doing infections that I would call
already makes them.
They would cover excreted do it.
Then I make another faction will Then?
Then I moved about.
They moved The building and loan building were bigger than a
foundation was hanging over about about 18.
We should really,
bro.
Yeah,
but electorally was able to pour more concrete in there.
Take care of that.
But it turned out okay.
And the belly was a good one.
And we made itself had big door.
You tow trucks.
And so it worked out good.
Well,
anyway,
my oldest of that.
And then two years later,
while Robin Tain and then two
years after that flip.
So they're all the same.
Oh,
well,
huh?
Why?
They blade down
those up.
Where is going to school?
Start school,
I guess with kindergarten and mother was
right about six blocks away.
Okay,
I love that.
But hey,
would walk to school.
Even the weather.
I mean,
That's why they did it.
So he started school,
and in the meantime,
I got it,
too.
I was in the chamber of cowards.
Witness.
Then I gotta do it.
We have,
apart from a client moving story and all
that.
Yeah,
uh,
sold examiners
really good witness because they have always
dude ranches in hotels and stuff that we're coming in on.
Uh,
it was a great place to sell.
No,
we're putting the whole of withdrawing pretty well.
Got cash poor,
not support your And so I
sold the business my part of the business.
And then I went back to college together.
Master degree.
I heard that if we were paid for you,
you know,
you have the whole summer off.
Yeah,
that sounds like a really good deal,
you know?
Yeah.
I fled with some were fishing,
right?
That that was and
eventually I worked with four.
Federer's for a while,
But then then I graduated,
and I needed a job,
So I got a job.
Carl said the ration co So any way moved to Carl?
Well,
well Oh,
So they're one year,
Roger.
All right,
go for earlier.
It's a New Mexico military looks like the long story
Short like a lie.
Although three grew up nicely.
And,
uh,
So the question is,
what happened to you?
Wherever you go throw and the court from the time
when you have,
uh,
we never actually went toe Manhattan,
Kansas.
Why,
What boy was in high school
on?
Hey,
took up.
Well,
cross country running okay,
did quite well,
didn't he?
Got into that.
And,
uh hey,
uh,
you got it.
You got really well did really well in the mind.
Uh,
while run Well,
he hey,
set a record and hold that
today.
Really?
Do you know,
do you know what the time is or know about?
But it's pretty generationally hasn't today if we don't run the mile anymore,
All right.
Really?
Yeah.
So anyway,
he still has that record today.
That's cool.
Forever.
Wow.
What did what did they substitute it with?
Or do they just get rid of that and do a different discipline in Kansas?
No.
Oh,
is it interesting?
OK,
so then he went down.
You got You want to original sunning in Arkansas
and,
uh,
good.
Pretty well,
but they're,
you know,
you get no matter how good you get somebody better?
Sure.
Yeah,
there were,
but he didn't get a scholarship with Kansas State.
Who?
Uh well,
hey,
did all right way.
Didn't do real well.
Oh,
Anyway,
we're there for Have a great
year.
Well,
you got it.
That mess.
What?
She what She raised,
you know?
Okay,
animals.
I grab it.
So proud,
dog.
Okay.
And,
uh,
what?
We were in town on somebody's
dog.
So anyway,
she got three dogs.
It was awful.
Way have
built a There was a tool shed black clear in the
back with a big old house that had been build around
18 mighty.
I guess it was maybe a little later,
but it had a no carriage house.
Coup story,
Eric World.
It had two doors.
Had one in front one of the back and run your carriage in there.
And then there was a place where he could take the horse home aside.
You know,
they did cool.
My folks have been really nice.
They thought because my dad win the hatchery with
one time.
He thought when you
know about cretins,
how that game
And thank you later.
The thing about so big remember much about it.
with your eggs in there,
and then it would hold temperature shared out,
whatever happens.
Yeah.
And it was a rooster.
So,
anyway,
that was in labor and Arizona.
We've time.
I took a job in Mexico,
and then then I went back to graduate school.
Uh,
you were there for a couple of years.
And while we're there was a chicken,
so I made a bargain for it.
Looks like a war was coming,
mate.
Tricking house.
You have a place for the chicken,
the rooms to all this.
So that when we moved the Manhattan Kansas,
we had to take two chicken,
so they got to the man had your town,
and this guy would Yeah,
more loud.
Yeah.
So I had this pool fed.
I insulated four door.
Yeah,
that build up life around France
around there.
Chicken would get out,
you know?
Well,
the chicken one he would get on the Are you chasing
kids?
And,
uh,
they would run.
Hey,
running after all night?
No.
So I said,
hey,
you know,
look,
all you have to do people picked him from
when he traced them to win the and
they run.
So just taken hold his legs in.
You know you won't.
Right?
So I got you like they
were big like this,
and he went out with one lip.
Yeah.
Anyway,
then Robin got dogs.
Okay,
along In the meantime,
this is a fairly decent story.
The neighbors,
the neighbors next to us.
And then they were on the corner,
and they had a slumming pool back.
Nobody will.
Yeah,
okay.
It was a big building And what it was
ground low.
So anyway,
they had a flood tonight around 1955.
That a great flood.
I mean,
it flooded downtown,
the whole downtown.
Oh,
good side of town It was.
At least I did deep on in town.
And,
of course,
the house we had had a bracelet flooded that.
Yeah,
there was Bud much still on the ceiling of the racial,
which we cleaned off room stuff.
But anyway,
it had raised the level of the yard so that the
sidewalk was at one level,
ground way.
Take care of that.
You're fired.
We're dead.
Dick.
It was It was a shovel.
In a way,
there was a loaf life in the back.
That's perfect place.
Just take a little of that.
Your heart put it in this low foot.
Wait for the deal.
And that's when on for much We finally got the yard
where it was down free time,
Yaar.
Yeah,
Go got it down where it was level with the
men we replant.
It turned out good.
Anyway,
where you're filled up Too slow for you.
Well,
uh,
before that happened,
Oh,
while we were doing it was came Crystal.
It's time we went down there.
My folks,
they were living down there.
So we have gone on and had to do something with chicken.
Well,
the chicken with a problem because Kroll,
Right?
So anyway,
so when they said they would never
wake up bad,
huh?
On the way back,
we've got a big snowstorm on the valley.
Western Kansas.
Yeah,
well,
way when he had a gun,
I have Finally,
Snow got day for her.
And for that put chains on the car on,
uh,
way snow Got the wrong guy.
Say,
just build the train.
Well,
my father came to a little town called so late.
Um,
they have the snow was blowing across there on
elevator.
Yeah,
wearing elevator,
the snow tires.
Oh,
Jeez,
there were no way 10 for a gander at that.
Yeah,
well,
there were a big follow snow,
and there was a motel there.
Gore process climb across the snow parts.
In the meantime,
a lot of other trucks and stuff.
Highways have been abandoned.
Yeah.
And going motive
on,
uh,
full of people,
you know,
they run a man.
All right.
A long,
long story short.
They were trying to place these only people in home.
Hey.
Well,
there was another.
There was another Couple it with a couple.
There was There was a 35 of us.
Okay,
free out.
So they said,
Well,
we have a place over here
down.
Actually,
it was a low ground house.
Okay,
careful.
And,
uh,
you have a a sheriff's car.
Got got our stuff into this,
Including this couple.
Okay.
Yeah.
Clown car,
Sheriff Deputy.
Oh,
yeah.
Anyway,
we go to this underground house this late in,
have room for nine people,
so I said,
Well,
I know another place.
Sheriff says we all climb back in the car
to get to this place.
You have to go through yard he attained on this card.
Two people yard.
Yeah,
we finally got to places with this lady.
Her name was roadie.
Okay,
Jenna,
Leg home.
We're going home.
Yeah.
Razor fools,
I scream.
Oh,
wow.
After we find the smell out
and wait car started.
No idea how.
All right?
No one was killed,
the entire blown in there,
killed in a fire.
Oh,
wow.
I drink it out.
She's Yeah.
Well,
anyway,
we finally got home.
Lonely old chicken.
Oh,
no.
Yeah.
You You're happy?
Wait.
Our relationship with them.
What kind of went down?
Because what happened then was a big rain.
And where we have quelled in it was it was no higher than their
swimming through.
Okay,
the rain came on.
Marshall.
That's right.
Ruin There.
Who?
Oh,
no.
Yeah.
Okay.
There's a lot of people,
right?
Work?
Yeah.
Rendered.
I heard that Rob got these old
before eight.
And we have this where there's chicken and then no damn nose on that.
Okay?
You know,
I never I never saw it.
All three of you.
It was like a chain link fence.
Or like a wood fence.
Yeah,
the changeling funds.
So I couldn't do that.
So we finally got some plunging the country agreed to take three gold.
Yeah,
I took her for a Yeah,
it was over after chicken and three dogs.
I mean,
and of course,
then the boys were into literally Okay.
Oh,
that's so that was
a pretty good life.
Well,
they were growing up.
I'm trying to think.
What?
What else?
Sorry about that,
Robin.
She was a teenager.
Humor.
Well,
probably loved one of that time.
Feels junior okay.
Or maybe
But she had a boyfriend who was black.
Well,
that you know that.
What?
Okay.
Anywhere.
I got a job in Texas.
So we moved down here?
Yeah,
in the rain.
Time,
of course.
Uh,
Carl was born,
so we were happy.
They were four.
Okay.
It was Oh,
yeah.
234 And so we were only moved down
here.
No.
As the years went by,
we moved down here.
I can't.
And they stayed up there because Lane was in
college.
Robin was a senior,
I think.
Wait for me,
Cooper Corporation.
I could do okay.
Every educational development restored
and way we're contracting the whole one of
workshops stuff for,
uh,
part of education.
They were going up the aisle.
Well,
they're uh,
rascal,
We need some kind of where we could
gramps reform this corporation.
Well,
well,
well.
There forever.
Oh,
hero.
So when I came down here,
I just moved down here with it.
Okay?
Robin Wright,
you graduated K state Kansas.
Blaine,
you're going a job.
Hey,
right.
Droid from college.
He got a job with
came or what?
Work.
Okay,
so here they were gone one anyway.
Dreadfully run.
Oh,
my wife.
My reward.
Hey,
no.
So here.
Oh,
go.
Yeah.
Heart stopped growing.
What?
They were You know,
we are where we go from there.
Oh,
Well,
actually,
then,
uh,
why did the older boy not married?
Joining the army?
He was in the armory and,
uh,
got married while I was in the army.
Yeah,
they said him Good turkey.
Okay,
so he was their northern part of Turkey
where they were flying on the Russian.
Okay,
I,
uh radar.
I don't know exactly.
You know,
he was there for a year.
Okay,
on,
uh,
Robert graduated.
Mostly.
Didn't get weird.
She got drowned preaching Hayes.
Okay.
No.
Moved out there on her.
Okay.
Rate way got into that.
Were gutted.
That hotel.
Fine before Ken Brown here.
And,
uh,
no,
before language service.
Okay,
so now you get taken time.
Anyway,
we have a hotel up right earlier.
Yeah,
they fill in a couple of jungle love you.
Have you running the bar?
She was waiting table?
No,
but then she if you got a job with wine,
don't go turned out
way.
Have a good time.
Yeah,
I think of the second summer.
She got a gun.
Okay.
All the great times flooded.
Come down here with me.
And,
uh,
here's to crow for your good.
You got the wrong crowd off chances.
The,
uh,
got drove with low on.
They sent him to boys home,
huh?
If you don't mind me asking what caused him to get sent there?
What did you do?
Well,
it's something I have to do with tease.
Okay.
Basically,
stolen computer broke it.
I see who was in wrong crowd.
I met a girl.
Uh,
they hit it off,
so he just disappeared.
He would like he was like a junior high school.
They went down to what?
We're she wasa way went down,
Got him,
brought him back.
Yeah.
No.
So that was when I came down here are brought
and,
uh hey,
stayed the trailer.
He got a job construction ride.
Yeah,
uh,
while the car Robert a thunder word.
Okay.
And then one day he disappeared.
That's OK.
You were just gone throughout the work.
Interesting.
Yeah.
Brad?
Uh huh.
You got three.
So,
anyway,
he disappeared.
Went back to camp.
No job was like one of these.
Okay.
Like that love alone.
Laurie became the manager.
Really?
Oh,
yeah.
It must be pretty good.
Hey,
Mandy.
Wedneday's a couple of
Mexican restaurants.
They got married.
This whole girl.
Okay?
It was awful not to the wedding way big.
Yeah,
it's folks.
Her folks had money with their She just wanted to get out of the house.
Okay.
You didn't want to get married.
Interesting.
Yeah.
So messy,
right?
Yeah.
Anyway,
fine.
Directionally.
Well,
hey.
Involved my older son.
In the meantime,
go job was while company.
Okay.
And I had worked with well,
won't time.
And,
uh,
so no.
Hey,
we're looking for a job so often.
Job corps.
Still there?
Okay.
Ever with the year.
Oh,
jeez,
that's cool.
My older son second son worked together.
Yeah,
that's cool.
Yeah.
Saying company.
They drive the same.
That's cool.
My older son is Super Rider,
so give him a big diesel pickup.
Oh,
cool.
Yeah.
Yeah,
Well,
yeah,
that's cool.
And what is the younger son do?
Did he just Does you Do they work,
like,
just for the same company,
or do they work on,
like,
the same crew?
Like Do they work?
They see each other.
Oh,
sweet.
Every day.
Yeah.
Thank you.
Well,
he just planted a really weird work.
Okay,
Let's go.
Yeah,
he can't stand to be working.
Right.
So with the Boston.
Yeah,
I would love to have people Who,
right?
Yeah,
that's good.
Oh,
yeah,
that's good.
Do it in a great time.
He,
uh this girl that he had gone back in high
school?
Yeah,
down Oklahoma.
He's gotten in touch with her and she got ahead of the war.
He didn't know went down.
They got very cool.
It all just worked out.
Yeah,
Yeah.
No.
Oh,
that's work.
That's where they are,
Not some Robin.
Talk to gold.
You're retired now.
Okay.
What?
She teach special ed.
That's cool.
Like all grades are like high school middle school.
I'm a tree todo o great.
But in the end,
they lived in hell.
Is Kansas school right across three?
Of course.
No.
So that was a big deal.
Yeah.
So see her the last 10 years.
Oh,
nice.
Yeah,
Well,
deal.
Yeah.
Go home for lunch.
Oh,
yeah.
So she did.
All right.
Retired.
And my other son,
Kyle,
is,
uh,
ck.
Okay.
What happened to him?
Waas that move down here And then Claire and I got married.
Hey,
they know that,
you know.
And,
uh,
so he,
uh you got a little He was 15 goofy.
So size one Thio
come down.
Live with us now from day one to come live with that.
So Claire Herded?
Yeah,
right.
Yeah.
So I came down here room.
We re signed real.
The ranch were lived in.
You know,
uh,
college.
You re trying to do the ranch away.
You helped out on that way,
moved out.
There was a good range.
Yeah,
What then?
He went to school and her.
Okay.
What?
High school.
Yeah,
which is a black school.
What you didn't really wear
on?
Uh,
no.
Take back to regulated in turn
mouth one day to do enlisted in the Army.
Okay?
Yeah.
Huh?
No.
Anyway,
we should get involved in the armory.
We want to make sure it was healthy and everything.
We gave him a whole bunch of vitamins.
Yeah,
First thing they did was the right.
yeah.
He'll figure him out.
Don't do that.
Take everything away from here.
Yeah,
they were in the Army.
Well,
they said more Lewis works.
My dad was stationed there.
Yeah.
Hey.
Was there for a while?
A year?
So what is that thing
called it a Mazda.
Our extra with their something.
Okay.
Got a sports car yet?
Perhaps.
Yeah.
Miatas air the small one.
Okay,
but in a way,
Hey,
you there for a while?
Then they sent in Beijing with the United
Nations.
So he was over there for a while.
In the sewer is okay.
Is ever really were fighting with the Egyptian
right?
United Nations with middle of that.
Okay.
Yeah,
they are.
Do all right here.
What is it exactly?
Sure.
Yeah.
When a number of thinks.
But anyway,
then then when they came back.
Hey,
you okay?
You don't agree there in the county.
And then one day announced today we're going to go to UT.
Who?
Yeah,
uh,
Lenny.
You went already?
Well,
the first thing he went up to Denver.
My mother there need you side to you get a job in Denver.
But he he was congratulated.
County did one of jobs whenever they are.
Yeah.
So we are turning back,
You know,
them well went over you t Okay.
Degree on last year.
Yeah,
but the wait time on a while.
This is all going on.
He decided he would travel around the world.
So sweet.
Oh,
yeah,
Yeah.
Go.
Well,
you did that for a while.
Then he met.
So oh,
three.
You go back,
you go to C T.
A.
He went to work.
They,
uh
well,
he was there downtown,
down downtown,
down building our calls with no big hole.
Okay.
The chase building?
Yeah.
Does he work for Deloitte?
Uh,
did you work for Deloitte?
Yeah.
Yeah,
that's cool.
I have some friends that were Yeah.
Yeah.
So it was there for a while.
Let's,
um,
tell she was really Yeah,
actually,
Ariel.
Okay.
Um,
so they No,
they lived together for a while,
and then she was transferred.
All scary.
Oh,
so I said,
Okay,
I'm going along.
So they went down to Australia.
Wanted you never get a job.
Okay,
so then they got to where they were getting along,
Or so some other guy in this conflict
anyway,
then he just started to travel around to go.
Don't worry.
Went to Israel.
Well,
you're okay.
No one.
What type of Thailand and met this girl.
Where?
Okay.
Yeah.
All right.
Well,
he's in Thailand.
We'll be back next week.
Okay?
Yeah,
because they live in my job.
Oh,
so they're just They're just traveled there with her?
Yeah,
for sure.
Hey,
says that you got three wars.
Yeah,
Uh,
your own school.
I said,
Well,
the graduate we're gonna move to Oh,
cool.
Yeah,
I don't Yeah,
yeah,
yeah.
Then it's a problem around.
You know what?
Sure.
I don't.
Yeah.
If they do,
maybe you have a cool place to visit for a little bit.
Yeah,
I can imagine.
Takes a long time.
You don't You don't like to travel that far.
No.
Yeah.
No,
that's a long time.
Well,
anyway,
that flood
had 34?
No,
not a girl.
Huh?
Daughter.
She lives in Maine.
She has two or three children were at main.
Do you know it's some sort of portal?
Okay.
Sure.
I used to live in me,
too.
You'll go for She was good doing it.
She was going before pay for okay.
You doing pretty damn alert.
She met this guy.
He was a P E major.
Yeah.
Will feel from Maine.
You know what I'm doing it for?
All right,
A little bit different.
Yeah.
You know,
that's very cool.
So she's doing all right then.
The oldest son lives in Lawrence,
Kansas.
He he's in the pepper so
food.
Okay.
Yes.
Yeah.
Interesting.
Yeah,
The other woman.
I went to a trade school.
He's a lot of body guy.
Yeah,
that's cool.
Blake had $2.
One of them.
She's a library and then was called.
Yeah.
Okay.
That's good.
Yeah,
that's on something younger fan for
about Oh,
Fleet trap me.
Oh,
wow.
It's a hard language.
Heard toe learns.
That's good.
So and then Robbins,
our oldest son.
Well,
son,
you have a son and daughter.
Fun is I work for an oil.
They have your children living,
Ellis.
Okay,
They're big right now.
They're all in rentals.
Okay?
Yeah.
It's supposed to be a big deal.
It's like Hayes
is where the college.
Pretty good.
Size.
Yeah.
What about 17?
So Ellis is,
like,
not that far away.
Oh,
yeah,
Yeah.
Rentals.
Oh,
for sure.
School system better?
Okay.
Yeah.
So now they somebody house sale,
for one thing.
Yeah.
That's smart,
though.
Supposed to be the good investment.
Smart investments.
Yeah.
Yeah,
I tried that.
Did you?
Yeah.
Good band.
Different.
Well renders.
Yeah,
I know how that goes.
You gotta go break.
Suppose the RV parks are the way to go because all you have to do is rent out the space.
They have to provide everything else.
And,
uh,
guess it's a lot easier.
No.
Well,
in this case,
yeah,
that's gonna be a lot like you.
Yeah,
that's great.
Yeah.
Yeah,
they get some of that.
You think they're going wrong?
Well,
okay.
He works for an oil company.
Let us for years.
I don't know what he worked for him.
Yeah,
he has cows everywhere.
Okay,
Granddad was it was a president of the
bank during the
Yeah,
yeah.
Yeah.
So they have have your house,
So I think he's doing okay?
I don't think I don't think they have the oil wells tell he's
Asian oil.
Yeah,
s so it sounds like everyone's doing good.
Oh,
yeah.
They're all doing well.
Nobody.
Yeah,
that's the goal,
right?
Yeah.
That's what people do.
Yeah,
yeah,
yeah.
Absolutely.
That's just about covered everything for today.
Yeah.