we'll start recording here
start recording here
All right so All right So now I have to
wait
now I have to remember where we left off last
week
We're talking
Don't worry
We have got to um We had gotten to um
you got to the point where we're starting to talk
about we had gotten to the point where we're starting
to talk about um about your children
He talked a little bit about where you grew up
about your children
You talked a little bit about where you grew up
and then the point in your life where you were
starting to have children
Many you mentioned that you had And then the point
in your life where you were starting to have children
You mentioned that you had
No
He had three of them at the time and then
another one came a little bit later
So that's where you want
If you had three of them at the time and
then another one came a little bit later
So no if you want
If that's where you want
Yeah
I think that's a good place to start I think
Pick back up
Just Are you okay Oh So when they first moved
to Gunderson it was in the in the fall
no
In the fall on then my older And then my
oldest my first boy was born in September a boy
was born in number
Okay and then we had to And then we have
to make it through that winter
It was really really cold at winner
But he did all right
make it through the winter with really really cold winter
He did all right
And my dad and my granddad were so excited because
we had a boy I have my dad like Grandad
were so excited because the other boy and uh so
so But we did all right
And then the second year we But we did all
right
And then the second year we I think it was
a cord
The end of the second year
We way build a house and moved in out of
the trailer
I have no idea what happened to the trailer
I think it was toward the end of the second
year way build a house and moved in our trailer
I have no idea what happened to the trail
Let any way way But anyway we uh we will
did to this house and that was it was kind
of needed
It was a one bedroom to bedroom we moved into
this house
It was a one bedroom too upstairs in a full
mason which was made into an apartment which we uh
we read it
Finally
upstairs in a full basement which was made into apartment
with three
We read it But it was it was a pretty
pretty neat
but it was it was for the party
The only problem with with it wasthe that The only
problem was with it Waas that the uh the uh
basement basement and the sewer system that when build in
Gunnison was probably round the turn of the century and
the sewer system when building guns was probably around the
turn of the century
Okay
and it was what they call open sewer
And it was what they call open
Okay And so so and the water table get above
the sewer their sewer it don't work the water table
get above the store this tour and don't work
Okay
And so that's what happened in the spring because the
snow would melt a lot of that
Then So what happened Frank Because snow would melt
Yeah allow that
at that point you got you got a real problem
in the basement trying to get it to flush and
all that At that point you got a real problem
but uh What and it was a problem a lot
And there was nothing they could do about it And
it was a a lot
They're nothing like d'oh
except to replace the whole sewer system Except replace the
whole sources right Sure they probably have you done yet
which they probably haven't done yet
I wouldn't I wouldn't think uh would
Anyway we uh it turned out really well and date
away We uh turned out rather well
I uh I brought a Oh yeah I brought the
a wielding welding that had been used for menus or
trucks where it was trucks where Ah no gas trucks
gas Actually like actually like uh you they call it
Elfi Gas
There we go
Oh you right
We call it fake
Here we go
Elfi Gas trucks
You this L ve gas strokes and used this thing
And so they wanted to sell the building and I
bought that thing and then So they want to sell
a building
And I bought that thing Moved it down there on
the back
moved it down there on the back of our place
So it was It was a big big building
And eventually I made it into a shopping then into
a business
And we had all the repair business back there
It was a late late will
Eventually I waded into job into a business way
Had all of repair business
But anyway But anyway uh there was a kind of
an adventure with that because I went up
Thio didn't measure the building
They told me what the two inches were
there was kind of the venture with that because I
went up to did major building
They told me with
So then I made a foundation poured concrete did that
So So then I made a foundation and poured concrete
Did that went So yeah the And uh we're doing
infections that I would call Ah I would do it
Infections and I would call ready mix and they would
cover
And I'd screed it and do it
And then I'd make another section
So then already makes them
They would cover excreted do it
Then I make another faction will Then then I moved
about
They moved the building and well the building was bigger
than Then I moved about
They moved The building and loan building were bigger than
a foundation was hanging over about about 18
yeah So it was hanging over Well about 18 inches
or so which was really a problem
Yeah We should really bro
Yeah but eventually was able to pour more concrete in
there
Take care of that
But it turned out okay
but electorally was able to pour more concrete in there
Take care of that
But it turned out okay
And the building was a good one
And the belly was a good one
And we made a shop that had big door because
you two were trucks
And we made itself had big door
You tow trucks
And uh so that workout
Good
Well anyway my oldest son then And so it worked
out good
Well anyway my oldest of that
And then two years later while then Robin Cane of
daughter
And then two years later while Robin Tain And then
two years after that flint came So they were all
over the same and then two years after that flip
So they're all the same
help
Oh Well in uh well Ah
huh Uh why they Why They uh Blaine got old
enough where I have gone to school
blade down those up
Where is going to school You start school I guess
Was kindergarten
I fooled
And uh but it was allowed Start school I guess
with kindergarten and mother was probably about six blocks away
at least
right about six blocks away
Okay And rough it
But hey would walk the school even in the winter
Time was kind of neat you know I mean that
the way they did things
I love that
But hey would walk to school
Even the weather
I mean That's why they did it
And so he started schooler So he started school And
uh in the meantime and in the meantime I got
into Ah ah
I was in the chamber of commerce business
And then I got into the I got it too
I was in the chamber of cowards
Witness
Then I gotta do it
ah we had We have furniture and appliances on dhe
willing the storage and all that stuff apart from a
client moving story and all that
on duh sold a janitor supplies Yeah uh sold examiners
uh which is really a pretty good business because really
good witness because they have always well they had all
these dude ranches in hotels and stuff that we're coming
in on
Uh it was a great place to sell
dude ranches and motels of stuff that we're coming in
And so it was a great place to sell
So janitor from Florida
So we got into all the business that we're doing
pretty well
Got cash report No we're putting the whole of withdrawing
Got cash poor uh cash not support cash short
not support your And so I sold the business my
part of business
And then I went back to college together master degree
And so I sold the business my part of the
business
And then I went back to college together
Master degree
Because I heard that I heard that uh if we
were a teacher you'd you know you have the whole
summer off if we were paid for you you know
you have the whole summer off
Yeah so it sounds like a pretty good deal you
know that sounds like a really good deal you know
Yeah
a friend of summer fishing
And I fled with some were fishing right well it
never turned out that way
But that's that was my father's time
That that was And eventually I uh and I work
for the four service for a while
But then and eventually I worked with four
Federer's for a while But then then I graduated and
I needed a job So then uh I graduated and
I needed a job so Ah I did got a
job in Carlsbad New Mexico
I got a job
Carl said the ration co So anyway that we then
we moved to Carl Bedwell
So any way moved to Carl Well well Uh Oh
So they're one year and so were there one year
on then went to Roswell New Mexico for several years
For Roger
All right go for earlier
what's the New Mexico military It's a New Mexico military
Like a long story Short right
Oh my
looks like the long story Short like a lie
All those three grew up nicely
Although three grew up nicely
And uh and so And uh So the question is
what happened to the word they go on Well that
we grow up
the question is what happened to you Wherever you go
throw And of course in the meantime we have
and the court from the time when you have Well
uh uh we eventually went toe a Manhattan Kansas on
Duh
we never actually went toe Manhattan Kansas
And why Why Blaine my oldest boy was in high
school
What boy was in high school Andi He took up
well on Hey took up
Well cross country running cross country running okay okay
And did quite well
Then he got into that did quite well didn't he
Got into that
and uh And uh and hey uh hey uh you
got it got really well did really well in the
mile
you got it
You got really well did really well in the mind
Ah well I'll run
Well he's hey set a record and Kansas and its
hold that today
Really Do you know what the time is No I
don't have to look it up Uh while run Well
he hey set a record and hold that today
Really Do you know do you know what the time
is or know about but But it's pretty generationally hasn't
today if we don't run the mile anymore of the
reason that he has today if they don't run the
mile anymore Uh yeah
All right
Really Yeah
So anyway he still has that record to this day
and will forever
So anyway he still has that record today
That's cool
Forever
Wow
What did What did they substitute it with What did
what did they substitute it with Or do they just
get rid of that and do a different discipline in
Kansas No
Oh is it No no it's uh Kilometers
Oh yeah
They don't run the mile around Columbus
interesting OK Yeah
Uh huh
So then he went down
You got so then he went down
You got Hey went to original thing in Arkansas You
want to original sunning in Arkansas and uh you did
pretty well but they're you know you get and uh
good
Pretty well but they're you know you get no matter
how good you get there somebody better
And there were better ones evidently
no matter how good you get somebody better Sure
Yeah there were But he did get a scholarship at
Kansas State
but he didn't get a scholarship with Kansas State
Who Uh well hey did all right way
Didn't do real well
Who uh you know in the garage
Well hey did all right but we didn't do real
well for them but he had a scholar
Uh and so anyway we're there for Oh Anyway we're
there for I guess seven or eight years Have a
great year
on
Duh
Robin was in the four H Club
Well She got in the end of that
That massive she Well she tried dogs
Okay on Duh
What could we were in town you got it
That mess
What She what She raised you know Okay animals
I grab it
So proud dog
Okay
And uh what We were in town on So somebody
said on somebody's dog
Are you ought to try Dog ran from really special
ones
So anyway she got three dogs
It was awful on uh It was awful
Way have built a long story behind that
We have built a There was a There was a
tool shed
Black
They're in the back with a big old house that
had been built around 18 tool shed black clear in
the back with a big old house that had been
build around 18 mighty
I guess they're on
mighty
I guess it was maybe a little later but it
had a It was in a maybe a little later
but it had a um no carriage house
carriage house
A two story carriage house on the back Coup story
Eric or the You know it had two doors
Have one of the front one of the back and
run your carriage in there
World
It had two doors
Had one in front one of the back and run
your carriage in there
And then there was a place where he could take
the horse And then there was a place where you
could take the horse out and then on the side
you know that's when he did things
home aside
You know they did Well anyway we also have tools
shared cool
and my folks has been really nice
They thought My folks have been really nice
They thought because my dad had been in the hatchery
but just one time and he thought my youngest boy
off Thio because my dad win the hatchery with one
time
He thought when you know about quickens and how that
happens all that
So we gave him an incubator
know about cretins how that game And thank you later
The thing about film leg I remember very much
A lot of what Their eggs in there
And then it would hold the temperature The thing about
so big remember much about it
with your eggs in there and then it would hold
temperature and shared up
One of them hatched
shared out whatever happens
Look
Yeah
And it was a rooster Of course
And it was a rooster
Yeah
So anyway when that was in when we were in
Arizona as well
In the meantime our shipping of we had So anyway
that was in labor and Arizona
We've time
Ah I took a job in uh I took a
job in New Mexico
And then Then I went back to graduate school in
in Arizona in Mexico and then then I went back
to graduate school
and uh Uh uh were there for a couple of
year
you were there for a couple of years
And while we're there was this got the chicken And
while we're there was a chicken So I made a
barn for so I made a bargain for it
Looks like a bar was gonna need it
Looks like a war was coming mate
Ah it was a chicken house
Tricking house
It had a place for the chicken the roost and
all this
You have a place for the chicken the rooms to
So then when we moved to Manhattan to Kansas So
that when we moved the Manhattan Kansas we had to
take the chicken
we had to take two chicken So when we got
to the when Hatton then if you're in town so
they got to the man had your town and this
guy would and this guy would you know it's five
o'clock in the morning
It was loud throw in the hold
Yeah more loud
Yeah
So they had this tool shed and I did it
I insulated So I had this pool fed
I insulated so dark
four door
And then we build a place around a fence around
there so that Yeah that build up life around France
around there
chicken would get out
You know Chicken would get out you know Well the
chicken would Well the chicken one hey would get out
in the yard you chase the kids he would get
on the Are you chasing kids and uh And uh
they they would run you know Hey run out here
all night they would run
Hey running after all night so I thought Hey you
know look and all you have to do No
So I said hey you know look all you have
to do people picked him from when he traced them
to win the Let's keep the chicken from getting when
he faces them get their wings up like this and
they would run
And so look it was just taken hold of wings
in
and they run
So just taken hold his legs in
You know He won't You know you won't
I can't do anything
Yeah so I did
I got that dude on
I have you Right So I got you like he
was big and I had it in like this and
he went on a bit
Rommel it like they were big like this and he
went out with one lip
Yeah
Anyway then Robin got dogs
Okay along In the meantime and it's still there today
Still a big star there today Anyway Then Robin got
dogs
And on the meantime uh this is fairly decent story
I guess this is a fairly decent story
the neighbors The neighbors have the neighbors next to us
and then they were on the corner the neighbors next
to us
And then they were on the corner and they had
a swimming pool there in the back that somebody had
felt poorly badly where it was a big bills of
lake swimming pool and they had a slumming pool back
Nobody will
Yeah okay
It was a big building and uh but it was
ground level
And what it was ground low
So anyway they had a flood tonight around 1955
That a great flood
I mean it flooded So anyway uh they haven't had
a flood in Manhattan in a around 1955
That a big flood
I mean it flooded Ah downtown the whole downtown home
It's a very good sized town and it was at
least that day defund in town
And of course the house We had had a basement
downtown the whole downtown
Oh good side of town It was
At least I did deep on in town
And of course the house we had had a bracelet
and it flooded that mason and there was mud mud
still over the ceiling in the races
And all that which we cleaned off made room stuff
down there
But anyway flooded that
Yeah there was Bud much still on the ceiling of
the racial which we cleaned off room stuff
But anyway it had raised the level of the yard
it had raised the level of the yard so that
the sidewalk was had one level and the ground was
like that
so that the sidewalk was at one level ground way
Take care of that
So we said Well we don't take care of that
My older son and I decided we would
You're fired
We were dating
Dig it
You know it was it was a shovel in the
wheelbarrow and were taken
And there was a loaf place in the back
We're dead
Dick
It was It was a shovel
In a way there was a loaf life in the
back
That's perfect place
And just take the level of the yard
We'll put it in this low place That's perfect place
Just take a little of that
Your heart put it in this low foot
which we did
And there's one nod from months Wait for the deal
And that's when on for much and we're filing up
the yard where it was down a free good side
yard We finally got the yard where it was down
free time Yaar
and uh Yeah and we got it Got it down
where it was Go got it down where it was
level with the sidewalk and then we replanted
Turned out good
Anyway we have filled up this low flee
level with the men we replant
It turned out good
Anyway where you're filled up Too slow for you
Well Well uh um before that it happened
uh before that happened Ah Oh while we were doing
while we were doing a little that it was came
Christmas time and we went down there is on a
it was came Crystal
It's time we went down there
My folks they were living down there
So to rid of my folks
They were living down there and so we had gone
and had to do something with the chicken
Well the chicken with a problem because we have gone
on and had to do something with chicken
Well the chicken with a problem because you know they
would crow right You know Kroll Right So anyway somehow
when they said they would neighbors they said to take
care of the chicken
So anyway so when they said they would never wake
up bad So when we got back uh on the
on the way back we got in a big snow
storm and huh On the way back we've got a
big snowstorm and down in western Kansas on the valley
Western Kansas
and we should have never gotten into that
Yeah well But uh wait When When Heads has got
into it and I have Finally the snow got deeper
and deeper and I put chains on the car way
when he had a gun I have Finally Snow got
day for her
And for that put chains on the car on uh
and uh and and the way and the snow got
deeper
Like I was saying you just kept going who had
changed way snow Got the wrong guy
Say just build the train
Well it finally came to a little town called somebody
Well my father came to a little town called so
late
and they had the snow would brawling across the other
Um they have the snow was blowing across there on
elevator on a sod on elevator
and Yeah uh grain elevator and it had grown and
the snow was least tire
That feeling
wearing elevator the snow tires
Oh Jeez There was no way that was the end
of that
there were no way 10 for a gander at that
Yeah Yeah
well there were So there we were at a big
pile of snow a big follow snow and there was
a motel there
I go across this climb across the Snow Bank and
I was course in the meantime a lot of other
trucks and stuff and there was a motel there
Gore process climb across the snow parts
In the meantime a lot of other trucks and stuff
on the highway
They've been abandoned one
And so we wanted to this Highways have been abandoned
Yeah
And going into this motel motive on uh and uh
it was full of people
There was a lot of people in there full of
people you know They brought him in
you know they run a man
All right
So anyway uh breaking a long long story short
A long long story short
The uh they were trying to replace these All these
people in homes in town
They were trying to place these only people in home
Hey
Well Well there was another
There was another couple with a couple
There really was
there was another
There was another Couple it with a couple
There was There was 35 of us and another car
There was seven There was a 35 of us
Okay uh three children
free And uh out
and so they said Well we have a place over
here that So they said Well we have a place
over here down
Actually it was a low ground house
Okay it was a where they had dug down
And actually it was a blow ground house for anyway
Loaded That
They said the sheriff will tell them
Get you
careful
And uh And uh So the sheriff game he had
a you have a uh the sheriff's car
And then we got got all her stuff into this
thing including this couple
Have no idea how
a sheriff's car
Got got our stuff into this Including this couple
Okay
Yeah
Clown car Sheriff Deputy
Oh yeah
Yeah there was
There was a sheriff in the density
There were nine people in that car
Anyway we we go this this underground house and this
leg didn't have room for nine people
Anyway we go to this underground house this late in
have room for nine people So you said Well I
know another place
The sheriff said so so I said Well I know
another place
Sheriff says we all climb back in the car and
he forget to this place she had to go through
the yard
He had changed on this car
we all climb back in the car to get to
this place
You have to go through yard he attained on this
card
God driving through funerals yards in there Two people yard
Yeah because the snow was so deep and we finally
got to the places with and this lady her name
was Rosy Red we finally got to places with this
lady
Her name was roadie
Okay which had a big home
Jenna Leg home
We're great gold home there
And a huge We're going home
Yeah
uh freezer full of Razor fools ice cream and steak
I scream
Oh wow
where there were a few days
After we find the smell out Well anyway after we
find this snow finally melted got it cleared up and
we have a car started
I have no idea
How does the snow filled the entire and loan in
there Fill the entire and wait car started
No idea how
All right No one was killed the entire blown in
there killed in a fire
engine compartment was no
And I had to dig it out of the damn
thing started
Yeah
Oh wow
I drink it out
She's Yeah
Anyway we finally got home and lo and behold our
chicken with dead
Well anyway we finally got home
Lonely old chicken
Oh no
Yeah
You You're happy Yeah right
Yeah right
I must have eaten him
Work Are your quick in one day
Well anyway Wait
our relationship with them what kind of went down Because
Our relationship with them
What kind of went down Because what happened then was
a big rain
what happened then was a big rain
And where we have filled in it was And where
we have quelled in it was it was now higher
than their swimming pool had a flint it was no
higher than their swimming through
Okay and the rain came and washed
All that's separating them ruined there
Who Oh yeah
the rain came on
Marshall
That's right
Ruin There
Who Oh no
Oh yeah yeah
Absolutely
Ruin them
Yeah
Okay
So then they suited Yeah they dropped the losses on
it and I had homered
Insurance
Renter's insurance I guess
What Uh Yeah
There's a lot of people right Work Yeah
Rendered
fall after whoever heard of that one
Well anyway Robin got these dogs before age I heard
that Rob got these old before eight
and we had this where there's chicken and vin
No damn dog could climb that fence
It was And we have this where there's chicken and
then no damn nose on that
Okay you know I mean never saw I never saw
anything like it in all three of them
You know I never I never saw it
All three of you
Like a brick in your climb that just like What
Is she weak fencer It was like a chain link
fence
Or like a wood fence
Yeah Yeah
Yeah the changeling funds
it was no crane long
Yeah
And so I couldn't I couldn't do that
So she finally got somebody in the country agreed to
take the three dogs that took care of her for
a So I couldn't do that
So we finally got some plunging the country agreed to
take three gold
Yeah I took her for a Yeah it was over
after chicken and three dogs
I mean and of course Then the boys were into
ah Little League and of course then the boys were
into literally Okay
and all of that stuff and Oh that's so ah
it was for the good life there
But that was a pretty good life
oh Well they were growing up trying to think What
what else could say about that they were growing up
I'm trying to think
What What else Sorry about that Ah Robin
She was a teenager
She was well Robin
Humor
Well probably about one that time
Feels a junior probably loved one of that time
Feels junior okay
or maybe a senior Or maybe junior I think
But she had a boyfriend who was black
Well that you know that my wife didn't think too
much of that
Well that you know that
What Okay
He was nice enough I guess
And uh anyway Anywhere
that went on for a while Then
Then I got a job at Texas A and M
So we moved down here I got a job in
Texas
So we moved down here and through all that in
the meantime of course Uh Yeah in the rain
Time of course
uh The those Uh Kyle was born Carl was born
in that process and they're So when we were in
Manhattan they were four children and he was little yet
so we were happy
They were four
Okay
It was Oh ready two or three or floor
yeah
234 And so we were only will down here
And so we were only moved down here
Well as the year went by when moved down here
and uh No
As the years went by we moved down here
I I came down and they stayed up there because
they I can't
And they stayed up there because uh Lane was in
college and Robin with a senior I think at that
point Lane was in college
Robin was a senior I think
So we had formed the covert corporation
Wait for me Cooper Corporation
I could do Uh to do educational evaluation was called
every okay
Every educational development resource educational development restored and uh way
we're contracting the whole lot of and way we're contracting
the whole one of workshops and stuff for workshops stuff
for uh of part of education
part of education
And they were going up the aisle
Uh They were going up the aisle
and uh was there uh Well they're uh Onda Rasca
putting on all this rascal Uh we need some kind
of ah We need some kind of where we could
where we could file gramps and on all that
So we formed this corporation on probably gramps reform this
corporation
Yeah we're going
Well well we wanted a trailer out
Well well well well well
There forever
Um Oh trailer It was funny but you know hero
So when I came down here I just moved down
here with it
I was matching
So when I came down here I just moved down
here with it
Okay Okay so they all stayed up there for a
while on Robert gradually I think
Robin Wright You know I graduated at K State Kansas
State you graduated K state Kansas
and Blaine
Blaine He got a job
Hey had graduated from college for them you're going a
job
Hey right
Droid from college
and he got a job with He got a job
with not came or came or yeah well worth what
Work
one Rose Okay of Nebraska on Duh
So he was He was gone so here they were
gone one anyway the eventually run of uh my wife
My God didn't wash
one anyway
Dreadfully run
Oh my wife
My reward
Hey And so I was here
no
So here
They were They were still up there
Oh Oh go squeaky thing
go
Yeah
I can't uh heart stopped growing up
Heart stopped growing
Well everywhere
What They were The uh You know kind of lee
out where we go from there
we are where we go from there
Uh Oh eventually
Well actually Then uh then uh mind got the older
boy got married why did the older boy not married
and joined the army
Joining the army So he was in the armory He
was in the armory and uh got married while I
was in the army
and they sent him
Could turkey
Yeah they said him Good turkey
Okay So he was dumped there and northern so he
was their northern part of Turkey where they were flying
on the Russians of what they're doing part of Turkey
where they were flying on the Russian
Okay Uh huh
I uh They had radar and stuff
radar
I don't know exactly what he did
He was there for a year or two
I don't know exactly
You know he was there for a year
Okay And uh on uh and then Robin graduated and
Robert graduated
we'll see
Yeah
Uh no she didn't get married yet
Mostly
Didn't get weird
Check out a job teaching and Hayes
She got drowned preaching Hayes
Okay
And uh we've got there and read her husband
No
Moved out there on her
Okay
In the meantime we got into that
We're have got into that hotel thing Rate way got
into that
Were gutted
That hotel
Fine that was very forward
Came down here before Ken Brown here
on DA And uh um no before language service
not really for of Lane one because servers was like
Okay so Okay so harder My roller and doesn't make
a whole lot of difference
now you get taken time
Anyway Anyway he uh we have a hotel up right
earlier
Yeah we had this hotel of hot right I spoke
about that earlier and so they they swim of cover
summers up there He was
He was running the bar and she was waiting tables
stuff
they fill in a couple of jungle love you
Have you running the bar She was waiting table No
But then Xiahe but then she if you got a
job at the Y m c a doing something like
that for a while if you got a job with
wine don't go But it turned out it turned out
you know we have a good time
Those summers
Yeah turned out way
Have a good time
Yeah and I think I was in the second summer
She got this guy and got married
I think of the second summer
She got a gun
Okay
Well the meantime Flynn did come down here and me
All the great times flooded
Come down here with me
and Ah And uh here's to crow hey
Had some trouble before he came down here
Got he got the wrong crowd of Kansas
for your good
You got the wrong crowd off chances
And the uh The uh got drove with law you
know And they sent him to uh got drove with
low on
They sent him to boys home huh boys hold for
a while
If you don't mind me asking what caused him to
get sent there If you don't mind me asking what
What caused him to get sent there What did you
do What did you do Well it's something I have
to do with tease
Okay
Well something had to do with keys
I don't think they've stolen
They had keys
They broke into a plate
I don't know Basically stolen computer broke it
I see who's in the wrong crowd on there
He met a girl who was in wrong crowd
I met a girl
and uh Uh and they hit it off
So he just disappear
You would like they hit it off so he just
disappeared
He would like It was like a junior high school
he was like a junior high school
and uh they went down to They went down to
Oklahoma
When we're what We're she loves we went down got
him brought him back
she wasa way went down Got him brought him back
Yeah
It was all uh hand
No
So So then when I came down here I brought
him that was when I came down here are brought
and uh and uh hey stayed in the trailer out
He got a job construction down and brian hey stayed
the trailer
He got a job construction ride
and uh Yeah uh a lot of car and brought
a thunder word
while the car Robert a thunder word
Okay
And ah
Then one day he disappeared
And then one day he disappeared
And the thunder word they just didn't show up The
work
That's OK
You were just gone throughout the work
Interesting
Oh yeah
You graduated from high school yet Yeah
Brad Uh huh
and eventually got greedy
You got three
So anyway he disappeared
Went back to Kansas So anyway he disappeared
Went back to camp
and got a job with like Wendy's No job was
like one of these
Okay
Like that like that
And then um it wasn't long before he became the
manager
Yeah
love alone
Laurie became the manager
Really Oh yeah
Way must be pretty good
Oh yeah
It must be pretty good
Hey Mandy
Wedneday's Yeah he managed
Wedneday's a couple of a couple of Mexican rifles
Mexican restaurants
Andi got married to some girl that it was off
went to the wedding
They had a big big wedding
Big time way
And his folks Her folks had money with their They
got married
This whole girl
Okay It was awful not to the wedding way big
Yeah it's folks
Her folks had money with their She just wanted to
get out of the house She just wanted to get
out of the house
Okay
if you didn't want to get married
You didn't want to get married
Interesting
Yeah
So messy right Oh Lord
And so that didn't last long
I don't know
Whatever happened to her
Yeah
Anyway Anyway would managing these things uh fine
and eventually
Hey Directionally
uh well hey
Got involved with my older son in the meantime Well
hey
Involved my older son
In the meantime had uh good job with a while
company go job was while company
Okay
and had worked for them for quite a long time
And I had worked with well won't time
And uh so uh And uh so no
Hey we're looking for a job so often
Job corps
Still there Okay
Ever front one
Hey look her job
So they offered him a job
He's still there
Whenever 15
You're a life
with the year
Oh jeez that's cool
My older son and the second son all work together
My older son second son worked together
Yeah Yeah Yeah same company
And they drive the same trap
And my older son is a super riser
So they give him a big diesel pickup
Oh yeah
Doing well
that's cool
Yeah
Saying company
They drive the same
That's cool
My older son is Super Rider so give him a
big diesel pickup
Oh cool
Yeah
Yeah Well yeah that's cool
What is a younger son do Did you just Do
they work like And what is the younger son do
Did he just Does you Do they work like just
for the same company or do they work on like
the same crew Like Do they work They see each
other
Oh sweet
just for the same company Or you work on like
the same crew like they were really was together
Oh sweet
Yeah Every day
Every day
Yeah
Thank you
And the heat
The flint is a real angel
We're worker
Oh yeah
Oh yeah Big time
Hey can't stand up to reworking
See And so when Well he just planted a really
weird work
Okay Let's go
Yeah he can't stand to be working
Right
So What A ll The Boston
She's wonderful
Yeah you know when he doesn't sit around like the
rest of right Yeah he's out there doing some fixing
something
All that
Oh yeah I think the world all of it
with the Boston
Yeah I would love to have people Who right Yeah
that's good
Oh yeah that's good
So Do it in the rain time in a great
time
Hey uh He uh this girl that he had gone
back in high school
this girl that he had gone back in high school
Yeah Uh she was down in Oklahoma down Oklahoma
and he somehow gotten touch with her and she got
it
Had a divorce
If he didn't have a husband only went down they
got married under which Crazy Yeah
He's gotten in touch with her and she got ahead
of the war
He didn't know went down
They got very cool
It all just worked out
Yeah Yeah
No
Uh so that's where that's where they are
Robin Trio
She talked
Bill Old You're retired now
Oh that's work
That's where they are Not some Robin
Talk to gold
You're retired now
Okay
What What She teach What What she teach fruitful area
especially Yeah Yeah
special ed
That's cool
You know like all grades are like high school middle
school
Like all grades are like high school middle school
I'm a tree todo o great
I think she did all that
Yeah but in the end they lived in the Ellis
Kansas in the schools right across the street
But in the end they lived in hell
Is Kansas school right across three Of course
So No
So that was a big deal
Yeah
So see her that was a big deal
And so she did her Probably for the last 10
years or so
She thought there right across the street
What a deal
Yeah Yeah
Oh yeah
the last 10 years
Oh nice
Yeah Well deal
Yeah
Go home for lunch
Oh yeah
Phil
So she did
All right
She's retired
So she did
All right
Retired
Yeah
And my other son Kyle is uh And my other
son Kyle is uh ah He's a c p a
ck
Okay
And what happened to him Waas That moved down here
And then Claire and I got married What happened to
him Waas that move down here And then Claire and
I got married
Hey and they I was and am they know that
you know
And uh so he uh And uh so he uh
you got a little He was 15 goofy
So size one Thio he got a little He was
15 and they're goofy when they're 15
So hey hey
Decided that he wanted Thio come down live with us
else one day
Want to come with liver that's so come down
Live with us now from day one to come live
with that
So glare and herded Claire Herded a teenager she hadn't
really planned you know Right You have a lot today
Yeah right
Yeah
So he came down here and then So I came
down here uh room
we decide to drill the ranch
We're living in town We re signed real
The ranch were lived in
You know in the college station uh college
and re tried to do the ranch
So we You re trying to do the ranch away
he helped on that
And then right And we moved out there
He he was a good ranch hand You helped out
on that way moved out
There was a good range
Yeah but then he went to school in her went
to high school with her which is a black school
What then He went to school and her
Okay
What High school
Yeah which is a black school
You did Really Where were you then Graduated one paying
them What you didn't really wear and uh no no
I take that back congratulated and turn and on Uh
no
Take back to regulated in turn and mouth one day
that he had enlisted in the Army
mouth one day to do enlisted in the Army
Okay Yeah
Oh Huh no
Anyway we sent him off to the Army Would want
to make sure he was healthy and everything
No
Anyway we should get involved in the armory
We want to make sure it was healthy and everything
We gave him a whole bunch of vitamins and stuff
And first thing they did restore those on Lindor
Try
You know I can't do that
Take everything away from cut their hair and all that
We gave him a whole bunch of vitamins
Yeah First thing they did was the right
Yeah yeah
He'll figure him out
Don't do that
Take everything away from here
Yeah they were in the Army
Haywood in the Army and uh ah they sent him
the Fort Lewis Washington
Well they said more Lewis works
My dad was stationed there
Yeah
Hey
Was there for a while A year So Hey was
there for a while a year So broader
What was that thing called It bothers you what is
that thing called it a Mazda
our ex Emlyn or something of a sports car Our
extra with their something
Okay
Got a sports car yet Yeah
Yeah a lot from God
One of the other guy Perhaps
Yeah
Miatas air the small one
Okay sold
Put it away
Hey uh hey
Would ever for a while
And then they but in a way Hey you there
for a while Then they sent in Beijing with the
United Nations
that sent into Egypt with the United Nations
So he was over there for a while in the
Suez is ever a lease and we're frightening with you
Drips in another or whatever
You know from the United Nations with the middle of
that
So he was over there for a while
In the sewer is okay
Is ever really were fighting with the Egyptian right United
Nations with middle of that
Okay
So he spent a long time over there Yeah and
in the r rated
Didn't seem to do all right
I did not hear what is what he did exactly
they are
Do all right here
What is it exactly Sure
guarded I guess
Yeah
When a number of thinks
But anyway But anyway then then when he came back
then then when they came back
Hey uh went to a and M
Man uh Hey you okay I got a degree there
in accounting You don't agree there in the county
and then one day announced that he was going to
go to UT And then one day announced today we're
going to go to UT
Who you know take a step down
You know Yeah look uh killed any
uh Lenny
He went over the well You went already Well the
first thing it hey went up to Denver
My mother was up there
He decided you should get a job in Denver but
he the first thing he went up to Denver
My mother there need you side to you get a
job in Denver
But he it was you know it was graduated in
accounting
he was congratulated
County You're getting one of those jobs whatever they often
here
And so did one of jobs whenever they are
Yeah
So hey came back
we are turning back And then then when I went
over to you t You know them well went over
you t Okay
degree on masters and uh yeah yeah yeah
Degree on last year
Yeah But in the meantime but the wait time on
a while
This is all going on
He decided he would travel around the world
So sweet
Oh yeah and while this was all going on he
decided he would travel around the world
Oh yeah Yeah
Yeah
Um uh Go
Well Well yeah
Hey did that for a while and then he met
some every day
you did that for a while
Then he met
So oh three
Got racking after he got a C v A You
go back you go to C T
A
He went to work from accounting out with in Dallas
He went to work
They They uh um only was there in downtown Dallas
downtown dollars building
Our order calls with a big hole in it
well he was there downtown down downtown down building our
calls with no big hole
Okay
The chase building I guess I don't work for huh
Did you work for Deloitte Yeah
Yeah Yeah
Does he work for Deloitte Uh did you work for
Deloitte Yeah
Yeah that's cool
I have some friends that were you know what That
Oh yeah
So he was there for a while and he went
from film gal
She was She was really sharp
Feel the Yeah
Yeah
So it was there for a while
Let's um tell she was really Yeah actual Ariel actually
Ariel
Okay
and over a Um so they uh they live together
for a while and everything
No they lived together for a while and then she
was transferred
All scary
And then she was transferred to Australia Oh so I
said Okay I'm going along
So they went down to Australia
Wanted you never get a job
Okay on So he said OK I'll go along
So they went down to are fairly one
He never got a job down there
Okay so then they got to where they weren't getting
a loan or something
so then they got to where they were getting along
Or so Some other guy under the picture I think
some other guy in this conflict But anyway then he
discarded travel around for Gore on a wary When we
went to Israel anyway then he just started to travel
around to go
Don't worry
Went to Israel
you weren't a rower and funny Well you're okay
No one
went to Thailand Thailand and left this girl wearing her
What type of Thailand and met this girl
Where Okay
Yeah
Their family are right now there Kyle
All right
Well he's in Thailand
We'll be back next week
But they live with my government now
Well all her folks live over there and he says
that when you one day when they got three boys
We'll be back next week
Okay Yeah because they live in my job
Oh so they're just They're just traveled there with her
Yeah for sure
Hey says that you got three wars
and uh their own high school Now Yeah Uh your
own school
you should want to graduate
We're gonna move Thio Thailand
I said Well the graduate we're gonna move to Oh
cool
Yeah This I don't know
Wait get cured it
It's one is treat
Yeah I don't Yeah yeah yeah
uh ready to get to travel around Then it's a
problem around
and whatnot
But uh You know what you know this isn't that
much to do
Sure
I don't say
Will it take 21 hour to get there Yeah
You know like to travel that far
No airplane
Oh no
I don't
Yeah
If they do maybe you have a cool place to
visit for a little bit
Yeah I can imagine
Takes a long time
You don't You don't like to travel that far
No
Yeah
Oh I know that
No That's a long time
that's a long time
Well anyway that Carter I think that uh Well anyway
that flood had 34 Flint had uh three or four
children one of whom died on uh uh It's not
got a girl
No not a girl
Uh Huh his daughter Daughter
uh fiddlers in Maine
She'd have two or three children She lives in Maine
She has two or three children were at main
Do you know itself
Trying Portland that uh against the name of the place
it's some sort of portal Okay
Sure
I used to live in me too
Yeah I feel very time died down from
Oh I say that
You'll go for I guess you would report
Hey She was good doing it
She was going before pay for okay
You doing pretty damn alert
if you're a good daughter she would go into four
page for all you're doing free dental or something
And she met this guy
He was a p E major
She met this guy
He was a P E major
Yeah
And what feelings remained I don't know what you're doing
at Fort Hayes right Will feel from Maine
You know what I'm doing it for All right A
little bit different
Yeah
A little bit different
And uh and so I don't know what he does
now
Yeah I have no idea what you know
They had three or four children You know that's very
cool
So she's doing all right then
The oldest son so she's doing all right
Then
The oldest son was lives in Lawrence Kansas
He lives in Lawrence Kansas and he he's in the
pepper he's in the cattle business
So fat food or something so food
Okay
I guess he's doing all right
Yeah
Yes
And then the other one is not over
Interesting
Yeah The other woman
Went Thio Trade School
He's usually auto body Guy
I went to a trade school
He's a lot of body guy
I guess he's doing all right
Yeah
Yeah that's cool
Blake had $2
Blaine Blaine had two daughters
One of room
Uh One of them
she's a librarian and She's a library and then was
called
Wisconsin in Madison
Yeah
And uh Yeah
she's pregnant
Finally after all these years all they're so happy on
the youngest one is in Japan
She's invented your fan for about 20 years
Okay
That's good
Yeah that's on something younger fan for about Oh Freak
Fleet Well you have the very well they say Oh
yeah
trap me
Oh wow
It's a hard language
Heard toe learns
That's good
Yeah
So And then Robbins and then Robbins her oldest son
her son had a son and a daughter
The fun is our oldest son
Well son you have a son and daughter
Fun is of work for an oil company
I work for an oil
They have two or three children
They have your children They live they live in Dallas
And living Ellis
Okay there there
Begin
Right now they're all in tow
Rental property
They're big right now
They're all in rentals
Okay Okay lying You know Right It's a good deal
It's like uh Yeah
It's supposed to be a big deal
Yeah
It's like Hayes's is where the college is A pretty
good size college
So what about 17 Hayes is where the college
Pretty good
Size
Yeah
What about 17 And so Ellis is like So Ellis
is like 10 miles
Oh yeah
And it's perfect you know and for rentals
not that far away
Oh yeah Yeah
Rentals
Oh for sure
You know we want to get out
Said you didn't want a school system better and all
that
Yeah
So now they somebody has a house for sale Somebody
died
School system better Okay
Yeah
So now they somebody house sale for one thing
I told you got about four or something
Yeah
Deal
You know like a damn nuisance
That's smart though
Supposed to be the good investment
Smart investments
Yeah
Yeah I tried that
Did you I tried that once
Did you Yeah
Yeah
Oh yeah
Well you know you got renters Ugo
Good band
Different
Well renders
Yeah I know how that goes
You know how that goes
You gotta go break
Sometimes they pay and you gotta go and click right
on that
No the RV parks on the way to go
Suppose the RV parks are the way to go because
all you have to do is rent out the space
They have to provide everything else
So we have to do is rent out the space
they they have to provide everything else
And uh I'm uh guess it's a lot easier
guess it's a lot easier
Yeah
No
Well in this case yeah that's gonna be a lot
like you
Yeah that's great
Yeah
Well in this case you have new maintenance stuff
Yeah that And they all run on light bulb without
your right
Stay
Think
Does grain
Yeah Yeah they get some of that
You think they're going wrong Well so they get some
of that but I think they're doing rolling
Well then
Her husband is a geologist
okay
He works for an oil company
Let us for years
He works for an oil company and he's been with
him for years
I don't know any work for them but then he
has college everywhere
I don't know what he worked for him
Yeah he has cows everywhere
Okay Okay
Is Granddad was uh was the president of the bank
and during the during depression until a lot roly properties
for nothing
Granddad was it was a president of the bank during
the Yeah yeah
Yeah
So they have Shenanigans
And so they have acreage everywhere
And I have cows
He has cows everywhere
have your house So I think he's doing okay So
you're doing all right again
Yeah
Uh I don't think I don't think they have the
oil wells themselves I don't think I don't think they
have the oil wells tell he's Asian oil
Yeah is in the oil mothers
Too little doing well
It's that kind of covers all over
Yeah and they're all doing well
Nobody's in jail
Yeah nobody's finally for bankruptcy s so it sounds like
everyone's doing good
Oh yeah
They're all doing well
Nobody
Yeah that's the goal right Yeah
and you hear a story
Well people who do you have that That's what people
do
Yeah yeah over Yeah yeah
Absolutely
That's just about covered everything for today
Yeah
I guess I'm about covered everything for today