start recording here.
All right,
so now I have to wait.
We're talking.
We have got to,
um you got to the point where we're starting to talk about
about your children.
You talked a little bit about where you grew up.
And then the point in your life where you were starting to have children.
You mentioned that you had.
He had three of them at the time,
and then another one came a little bit later.
So that's where you want.
Yeah.
I think that's a good place to start,
I think.
Oh,
when they first moved to Gunderson,
it was in the in the fall.
And then my oldest,
my first boy was born in September,
and then we had to make it through that winter.
It was really,
really cold at winner.
But he did all right.
And my dad and my granddad were so excited because we
had a boy and,
uh so But we did all right.
And then the second year,
we I think it was a cord.
The end of the second year.
We way build a house and moved in out of the
trailer.
I have no idea what happened to the trailer.
But anyway,
we,
uh we will did to this house,
and that was it was kind of needed.
It was a one bedroom to bedroom upstairs in a full
mason,
which was made into an apartment which we,
uh,
we read it.
Finally.
But it was it was a pretty pretty neat.
The only problem with with it wasthe that
the,
uh,
basement and the sewer system that when build in
Gunnison was probably round the turn of the century
and it was what they call open sewer.
And so and the water table get above the sewer,
their sewer,
it don't work,
Okay.
And so that's what happened in the spring because the snow would melt a lot
of that.
Then,
at that point,
you got you got a real problem in the basement trying to get it to
flush and all that,
but,
uh,
and it was a problem,
a lot.
And there was nothing they could do about it,
except to replace the whole sewer system,
which they probably haven't done yet.
I wouldn't I wouldn't think,
uh,
would.
Anyway,
we,
uh it turned out really well,
and I,
uh,
I brought a a wielding that
had been used for trucks where it was
Ah,
gas trucks.
Actually,
like,
uh,
you they call it Elfi Gas.
There we go.
L ve gas strokes and used this thing.
And so they wanted to sell the building,
and I bought that thing and then moved it down there on the back of our place.
So it was It was a big,
big building.
And eventually I made it into a shopping,
then into a business.
And we had all the repair business back there.
But anyway,
uh,
there was a kind of an adventure with that because I went up.
Thio didn't measure the building.
They told me what the two inches were.
So then I made a foundation and poured
concrete.
Did that went So And,
uh Ah,
I would do it.
Infections and I would call ready mix,
and they would cover.
And I'd screed it and do it.
And then I'd make another section.
So then then I moved about.
They moved the building and well,
the building was bigger than yeah,
So it was hanging over Well,
about 18 inches or so,
which was really a problem.
Yeah,
but eventually was able to pour more concrete in there.
Take care of that.
But it turned out okay.
And the building was a good one.
And we made a shop that had big door because you two were trucks.
And,
uh,
so that workout.
Good.
Well,
anyway,
my oldest son,
then And then two years later,
while then Robin Cane of daughter.
And then two years after that,
flint came,
So they were all over the same help.
Well,
in,
uh Ah.
Uh,
why they,
uh,
Blaine got old enough where I have gone to school.
You start school,
I guess,
Was kindergarten.
I fooled.
And,
uh but it was allowed probably
about six blocks away at least.
And rough it.
But hey,
would walk the school even in the winter.
Time was kind of neat,
you know?
I mean that the way they did things.
And so he started schooler,
And,
uh,
in the meantime,
I got into Ah ah.
I was in the chamber of commerce business.
And then I got into the ah,
we had furniture and appliances on dhe
willing the storage and all that stuff on duh
sold a janitor supplies,
uh,
which is really a pretty good business because,
well,
they had all these dude ranches and
motels of stuff that we're coming in.
And so it was a great place to sell.
So janitor from Florida.
So we got into all the business that we're doing pretty well.
Got cash report,
uh,
cash not support cash short.
And so I sold the business my part of business.
And then I went back to college together,
master degree,
Because I heard that,
uh,
if we were a teacher,
you'd,
you know,
you have the whole summer off,
so it sounds like a pretty good deal,
you know,
a friend of summer fishing.
And,
well,
it never turned out that way.
But that's that was my father's time.
And eventually,
I,
uh,
and I work for the four service for a while.
But then then,
uh,
I graduated and I needed a job,
so Ah,
I did got a job in Carlsbad,
New Mexico.
So anyway,
that we then we moved to Carl Bedwell.
Uh,
and so were there one year on,
then went to Roswell,
New Mexico,
for several years.
For what's the New Mexico military?
Like a long story Short,
right.
Oh,
my.
All those three grew up nicely.
And,
uh and so the question is,
what happened to the word they go on?
Well,
that we grow up.
And of course,
in the meantime,
we have.
Well,
uh,
we eventually went toe a Manhattan Kansas on Duh.
And why Blaine,
my oldest boy,
was in high school.
Andi,
He took up well,
cross country running,
okay.
And did quite well.
Then he got into that,
and,
uh,
and hey,
you got it got really well did really well in the mile.
Ah,
well,
I'll run.
Well,
he's hey,
set a record and Kansas and its hold that
today.
Really?
Do you know what the time is?
No,
I don't have to look it up,
but of the reason that he has today if they don't run the mile anymore
Uh,
yeah.
So anyway,
he still has that record to this day and will forever.
What did What did they substitute it with?
No,
no,
it's,
uh,
Kilometers.
Oh,
yeah.
They don't run the mile around Columbus.
Yeah.
Uh huh.
So then he went down.
You got Hey,
went to original thing in Arkansas,
and,
uh,
you did pretty well,
but they're you know,
you get no matter how good you get there,
somebody better.
And there were better ones evidently.
But he did get a scholarship at Kansas State.
Who,
uh,
you know,
in the garage.
Well,
hey,
did all right,
but we didn't do real well for them,
but he had a scholar.
Uh,
and so anyway,
we're there for,
I guess,
seven or eight years
on.
Duh.
Robin was in the four H Club.
She got in the end of that.
That massive she?
Well,
she tried dogs.
Okay,
on Duh.
What could we were in town on?
So somebody said,
Are you ought to try Dog ran from really special ones.
So anyway,
she got three dogs.
It was awful on,
uh,
long story behind that.
We have built a There was a tool shed.
Black.
They're in the back with a big old house that had been built
around 18 mighty.
I guess they're on.
It was in a maybe a little later,
but it had a,
um,
carriage house.
A two story carriage house on the back or the You know,
it had two doors.
Have one of the front one of the back and run your carriage in there.
And then there was a place where you could take the horse out and then on the side,
you know,
that's when he did things.
Well,
anyway,
we also have tools shared and my folks has been really nice.
They thought because my dad had been in the hatchery,
but just one time and he thought my youngest boy off Thio
know about quickens and how that happens all that.
So we gave him an incubator.
The thing about film leg,
I remember very much.
A lot of what?
Their eggs in there.
And then it would hold the temperature and shared up.
One of them hatched.
Look.
And it was a rooster,
Of course.
So,
anyway,
when that was in,
when we were in Arizona as well.
In the meantime,
our shipping of we had Ah,
I took a job in,
uh,
in New Mexico.
And then Then I went back to graduate school in in Arizona
and,
uh,
uh were there for a couple of year.
And while we're there,
was this got the chicken,
So I made a barn for it.
Looks like a bar was gonna need Ah,
it was a chicken house.
It had a place for the chicken,
the roost and all this.
So then when we moved to Manhattan to Kansas,
we had to take the chicken.
So when we got to the when Hatton,
then if you're in town and this
guy would,
you know,
it's five o'clock in the morning.
It was loud throw in the hold.
So they had this tool shed,
and I did it.
I insulated so dark.
And then we build a place around a
fence around there so that chicken would get out.
You know?
Well,
the chicken would hey,
would get out in the yard,
you chase the kids and,
uh,
they they would run,
you know?
Hey,
run out here all night,
so I thought,
Hey,
you know,
look and all you have to do Let's keep the
chicken from getting when he faces them,
get their wings up like this and they would run.
And so,
look,
it was just taken hold of wings in.
You know?
He won't I can't do anything.
Yeah,
so I did.
I got that dude on.
I have you like he was big and I had it in like this and he went on a
bit.
Rommel it and it's still there today.
Still a big star there today,
Anyway,
Then Robin got dogs.
And on the meantime,
uh,
this is fairly decent story.
I guess the neighbors have the neighbors next to
us,
and then they were on the corner and they had a swimming
pool there in the back that somebody had felt poorly,
badly,
where it was a big bills of lake swimming pool,
and,
uh,
but it was ground level.
So anyway,
uh,
they haven't had a flood in Manhattan in a around 1955.
That a big flood.
I mean,
it flooded Ah,
downtown,
the whole downtown home.
It's a very good sized town,
and it was at least that day defund in town.
And,
of course,
the house We had had a basement and it flooded that mason
and there was mud mud still over the ceiling in the races.
And all that which we cleaned off,
made room stuff down there.
But anyway,
it had raised the level of the yard so that the
sidewalk was had one level and the ground was like that.
So we said,
Well,
we don't take care of that.
My older son and I decided we would.
We were dating.
Dig it.
You know,
it was it was a shovel in the wheelbarrow and were taken.
And there was a loaf place in the back.
That's perfect place.
And just take the level of the yard.
We'll put it in this low place,
which we did.
And there's one nod from months and we're filing up the yard
where it was down a free good side yard,
and,
uh,
and we got it,
Got it down where it was level with the sidewalk and
then we replanted.
Turned out good.
Anyway,
we have filled up this low flee.
Well,
uh um,
before that,
it happened.
Ah,
while we were doing a little that it was came Christmas
time and we went down there is on a to rid of my folks.
They were living down there,
and so we had gone and had to do something with the chicken.
Well,
the chicken with a problem because,
you know,
they would crow,
right?
You know?
So anyway,
somehow,
when they said they would neighbors,
they said to take care of the chicken.
So when we got back,
uh,
on the on the way back we got in a big snow storm and
and down in western Kansas,
and we should have never gotten into that.
But,
uh,
wait When?
When Heads has got into it and I have Finally,
the snow got deeper and deeper,
and I put chains on the car and,
uh,
and and the
way and the snow got deeper.
Like I was saying,
you just kept going who had changed?
Well,
it finally came to a little town called somebody,
and they had the snow would brawling across the other
on elevator on a sod and,
uh,
grain elevator and it had grown and the snow was
least tire.
That feeling.
There was no way that was the end of that.
Yeah.
So there we were at a big pile of snow,
and there was a motel there.
I go across this climb across the Snow Bank,
and I was course in the meantime,
a lot of other trucks and stuff on the highway.
They've been abandoned one.
And so we wanted to this into this motel,
and,
uh,
it was full of people.
There was a lot of people in there,
you know,
They brought him in.
So anyway,
uh,
breaking a long,
long story short.
The,
uh they were trying to replace these All these people in
homes in town.
Well,
there was another.
There was another couple with a couple.
There really was.
There was 35 of us and another car.
There was seven,
uh,
three children.
And,
uh,
and so they said,
Well,
we have a place over here that it was a
where they had dug down.
And actually,
it was a blow ground house for
anyway,
Loaded That.
They said the sheriff will tell them.
Get you.
And,
uh,
So the sheriff game,
he had a,
uh,
the sheriff's car.
And then we got got all her stuff into this thing,
including this couple.
Have no idea how.
Yeah,
there was.
There was a sheriff in the density.
There were nine people in that car.
Anyway,
we we go this this underground house,
and this leg didn't have room for nine people.
So you said,
Well,
I know another place.
The sheriff said so we all climb back in the car and he
forget to this place she had to go through the yard.
He had changed on this car.
God driving through funerals yards in there because the snow was
so deep and we finally got to the places with and this
lady,
her name was Rosy Red,
which had a big home.
We're great gold home there.
And a huge,
uh,
freezer full of ice cream and steak
where there were a few days.
Well,
anyway,
after we find this snow finally melted,
got it cleared up and we have a car started.
I have no idea.
How does the snow filled the entire and loan
in there?
Fill the entire engine compartment was no.
And I had to dig it out of the damn thing started.
Yeah.
Anyway,
we finally got home and lo and behold,
our chicken with dead.
Yeah,
right.
I must have eaten him.
Work Are your quick in one day.
Well,
anyway,
our relationship with them what kind of went down?
Because what happened then was a big rain.
And where we have filled in it was it was now higher than their
swimming pool had a flint and the rain came and
washed.
All that's separating them ruined there.
Who?
Oh,
yeah.
yeah,
Absolutely.
Ruin them.
So then they suited
Yeah,
they dropped the losses on it and I had homered.
Insurance.
Renter's insurance,
I guess.
What?
Uh,
fall after whoever heard of that one.
Well,
anyway,
Robin got these dogs before age,
and we had this where there's chicken and vin.
No damn dog could climb that fence.
It was,
you know,
I mean,
never saw I never saw anything like it in all three of them.
Like a brick in your climb that just like What?
Is she weak fencer?
Yeah.
Yeah,
it was no crane long.
Yeah.
And so I couldn't I couldn't do that.
So she finally got somebody in the country,
agreed to take the three dogs that took care of her for a
and,
of course,
Then the boys were into,
ah,
Little League and all of that
stuff,
and ah,
it was for the good life there.
But,
oh,
they were growing up trying to think What what else could say about
that?
Ah,
Robin.
She was a teenager.
She was well,
probably about one that time.
Feels a junior or maybe a senior junior,
I think.
But she had a boyfriend who was black.
Well,
that you know that my wife didn't think too much of that.
He was nice enough,
I guess.
And,
uh,
anyway,
that went on for a while,
Then.
Then I got a job at Texas A and M.
So we moved down here and through all that in the
meantime,
of course,
Uh uh,
The those Kyle was born in that
process,
and they're So when we were in Manhattan,
they were four children,
and he was little yet ready two or three or floor.
And so we were only will down here.
Well,
as the year went by when moved down here and,
uh,
I I came down and they stayed up there because they,
Lane was in college and Robin with a senior,
I think at that point
So we had formed the covert corporation.
Uh,
to do educational evaluation was called every
educational development resource
and,
uh,
way we're contracting the whole lot of
workshops and stuff for of part of
education.
And they were going up the aisle.
Uh,
and,
uh,
was there,
Onda Rasca putting on all this?
Uh,
we need some kind of ah,
where we could file gramps and on all that.
So we formed this corporation on probably Yeah,
we're going.
Well,
well,
we wanted a trailer out.
Um,
trailer,
It was funny,
but,
you know,
So when I came down here,
I just moved down here with it.
I was matching.
Okay,
so they all stayed up there for a while on Robert gradually,
I think.
You know,
I graduated at K State,
Kansas State and Blaine.
He got a job.
Hey,
had graduated from college for them,
and he got a job with
not came or yeah,
well worth one Rose of
Nebraska on Duh.
So he was He was gone one anyway,
the eventually run of,
uh,
my wife.
My God didn't wash.
And so I was here.
They were They were still up there.
Oh,
go squeaky thing.
I can't,
uh,
heart stopped growing up.
Well,
everywhere.
The,
uh,
kind of lee out where we go from there.
Uh,
eventually.
Then,
uh,
mind got the older boy,
got married and joined the army.
So he was in the armory and,
uh,
got married while I was in the armory,
and they sent him.
Could turkey.
So he was dumped there and northern part of Turkey,
where they were flying on the Russians of what they're doing?
Uh huh.
They had radar and stuff.
I don't know exactly what he did.
He was there for a year or two.
And,
uh and then Robin graduated,
and we'll see.
Yeah.
Uh,
no,
she didn't get married yet.
Check out a job teaching and Hayes.
Okay.
And,
uh,
we've got there and read her husband.
In the meantime,
we got into that.
We're have got into that hotel thing that was very forward.
Came down here on DA
um,
not really for of Lane one,
because servers was,
like,
Okay,
so harder My roller
and doesn't make a whole lot of difference.
Anyway,
he,
uh we had this hotel of hot,
right?
I spoke about that earlier,
and so they they swim of cover summers up there He
was.
He was running the bar and she was waiting
tables stuff.
But then Xiahe if you got a job at the Y m c a doing
something like that for a while,
But it turned out it turned out,
you know,
we have a good time.
Those summers.
Yeah,
and I think I was in the second summer.
She got this guy and got married.
Well,
the meantime Flynn did come down here and me and
Ah,
hey.
Had some trouble before he came down here.
Got he got the wrong crowd of Kansas.
And the,
uh,
got drove with law,
you know?
And they sent him to,
uh,
boys hold for a while.
If you don't mind me asking what?
What caused him to get sent there?
What did you do?
Well,
something had to do with keys.
I don't think they've stolen.
They had keys.
They broke into a plate.
I don't know who's in the wrong crowd on there.
He met a girl,
and,
uh,
and they hit it off.
So he just disappear.
You would like It was like a junior high school,
and,
uh,
they went down to Oklahoma.
When we're she loves,
we went down,
got him,
brought him back.
It was all,
uh,
hand.
So then when I came down here,
I brought him,
and,
uh,
hey,
stayed in the trailer out.
He got a job construction down,
and brian and,
uh,
a lot of car and brought a thunder word.
Okay.
And ah.
Then one day he disappeared.
And the thunder word,
they just didn't show up The work.
Interesting.
Oh,
yeah.
You graduated from high school yet and eventually got
greedy.
So anyway,
he disappeared.
Went back to Kansas and got a
job with,
like,
Wendy's like that.
And then,
um,
it wasn't long before he became the manager.
Yeah.
Oh,
yeah.
Way must be pretty good.
Yeah,
he managed.
Wedneday's a couple of
Mexican rifles.
Andi got married to some girl that it was off,
went to the wedding.
They had a big,
big wedding.
Big time way.
And his folks,
Her folks had money with their She just wanted to get out of the
house if you didn't want to get married.
Oh,
Lord.
And so that didn't last long.
I don't know.
Whatever happened to her.
Yeah.
Anyway,
would managing these things,
uh,
and eventually.
Hey,
uh,
well,
hey.
Got involved with my older son in the meantime,
had,
uh,
good job with a while company and had
worked for them for quite a long time.
And,
uh so,
uh,
front one.
Hey,
look,
her job.
So they offered him a job.
He's still there.
Whenever 15.
You're a life.
My older son and the second son all work together.
Yeah,
same company.
And they drive the same trap.
And my older son is a super riser.
So they give him a big diesel pickup.
Oh,
yeah.
Doing well.
What is a younger son do?
Did you just Do they work,
like,
just for the same company?
Or you work on,
like,
the same crew like they were really was together.
Oh,
sweet.
Yeah,
Every day.
Yeah.
And the heat.
The flint is a real angel.
We're worker.
Oh,
yeah.
yeah,
Big time.
Hey,
can't stand up to reworking.
See?
And so when What?
A ll The Boston.
She's wonderful.
Yeah,
you know,
when he doesn't sit around like the rest of right?
Yeah,
he's out there doing some fixing something.
All that.
Oh,
yeah,
I think the world all of it.
So in the rain time Hey,
uh,
this girl that he had gone back in high school.
Uh,
she was down in Oklahoma and he somehow gotten touch with her and she
got it.
Had a divorce.
If he didn't have a husband,
only went down,
they got married under which
Crazy?
Yeah.
Uh,
so that's where that's where they are.
Robin Trio.
She talked.
Bill Old,
You're retired now.
What?
What she teach fruitful area,
especially?
Yeah,
Yeah.
You know,
like all grades are like high school,
middle school.
I think she did all that.
Yeah,
but in the end,
they lived in the Ellis Kansas in the schools,
right across the street.
So that was a big deal.
And so she did her Probably for the last 10 years or so.
She thought there,
right across the street.
What a deal.
Yeah,
Yeah.
Oh,
yeah.
Phil.
So she did.
All right.
She's retired.
Yeah.
And my other son,
Kyle,
is,
uh ah,
He's a c p a.
And what happened to him?
Waas That moved down here.
And then Claire and I got married and they I was and
am And,
uh so he,
uh he got a little He was 15 and they're goofy when they're
15.
So hey,
hey.
Decided that he wanted Thio come down live with
us else one day.
Want to come with liver that's so glare and herded
a teenager she hadn't really planned,
you know?
Right,
You have a lot today,
So he came down here and then,
uh,
we decide to drill the ranch.
We're living in town in the college station
and re tried to do the ranch.
So we he helped on that.
And then right,
And we moved out there.
He he was a good ranch hand,
but then he went to school in her,
went to high school with her,
which is a black school.
You did?
Really?
Where were you then?
Graduated one paying them and,
uh,
no,
no.
I take that back congratulated and turn and
and mouth one day that he had enlisted in the Army.
Oh,
no.
Anyway,
we sent him off to the Army,
Would want to make sure he was healthy and everything.
We gave him a whole bunch of vitamins and stuff.
And first thing they did restore those on Lindor.
Try.
You know,
I can't do that.
Take everything away from cut their hair and all that Haywood in
the Army and,
uh ah,
they sent him the Fort Lewis Washington.
My dad was stationed there.
Yeah.
Hey,
was there for a while a year?
So broader.
What was that thing called?
It bothers you,
our ex Emlyn or something of a sports car?
Yeah.
Yeah,
a lot from God.
One of the other guy sold.
Put it away.
Hey,
uh,
hey.
Would ever for a while.
And then they that sent into Egypt with the United
Nations.
So he was over there for a while in the Suez
is ever a lease,
and we're frightening with you Drips in another or whatever.
You know,
from the United Nations with the middle of that.
So he spent a long time over there and in the r
rated.
Didn't seem to do all right.
I did not hear what is what he did exactly
guarded,
I guess.
But anyway,
then then when he came back,
Hey,
uh,
went to a and M.
Man,
uh,
I got a degree there in accounting and then one
day announced that he was going to go to UT,
you know,
take a step down.
You know,
look,
uh,
killed any.
He went over the well,
the first thing it hey,
went up to Denver.
My mother was up there.
He decided you should get a job in Denver,
but he it was,
you know,
it was graduated in accounting.
You're getting one of those jobs,
whatever they often here.
And so hey,
came back.
And then then when I went over to you t
degree on masters,
and,
uh,
yeah,
yeah.
But in the meantime,
and while this was all going on,
he decided he would travel around the world.
Oh,
yeah?
Yeah.
Um,
uh,
Well,
yeah.
Hey,
did that for a while,
and then he met some every day.
Got racking after he got a C v A He went to work from
accounting out with in Dallas.
They,
um,
only was there in downtown Dallas downtown dollars building.
Our order calls with a big hole in it.
I guess I don't work for huh.
Did you work for Deloitte?
Yeah.
Yeah,
you know what?
That.
Oh,
yeah.
So he was there for a while,
and he went from film gal.
She was She was really sharp.
Feel the actual Ariel
and over a,
uh they live together for a while and everything.
And then she was transferred to Australia
on So he said,
OK,
I'll go along.
So they went down to are fairly one.
He never got a job down there.
Okay,
so then they got to where they weren't getting a loan or something.
Some other guy under the picture,
I think.
But anyway,
then he discarded travel around for Gore on a wary When we went to
Israel,
you weren't a rower and funny went to
Thailand,
Thailand and left this girl wearing her.
Their family are right now there,
Kyle.
We'll be back next week.
But they live with my government now.
Well,
all her folks live over there,
and he says that when you one day when they got three
boys and,
uh,
their own high school Now you should want to graduate.
We're gonna move Thio Thailand.
This I don't know.
Wait,
get cured it.
It's one is treat.
Yeah,
uh,
ready to get to travel around and whatnot.
But,
uh,
you know,
this isn't that much to do.
I don't say.
Will
it take 21 hour to get there?
Yeah.
You know,
like to travel that far.
No airplane.
Oh,
no.
I know that.
That's a long time.
Well,
anyway,
that Carter,
I think that,
uh,
Flint had,
three or four children,
one of whom died on uh uh,
It's not got a girl.
Uh,
his daughter,
uh,
fiddlers in Maine.
She'd have two or three children
itself.
Trying Portland that,
uh,
against the name of the place.
Yeah,
I feel very time died down from.
Oh,
I say that.
I guess you would report.
Hey,
if you're a good daughter,
she would go into four page for all you're doing free dental or
something.
And she met this guy.
He was a p E major.
Yeah.
And what feelings remained?
I don't know what you're doing at Fort Hayes,
right?
A little bit different.
And,
uh,
and so I don't know what he does now.
Yeah,
I have no idea what you know.
They had three or four children,
so she's doing all right.
Then.
The oldest son was lives in Lawrence,
Kansas,
and he he's in the cattle business.
So,
fat food or something?
I guess he's doing all right.
Yeah.
And then the other one is not over.
Went Thio Trade School.
He's usually auto body Guy.
I guess he's doing all right.
Yeah.
Blaine Blaine had two daughters.
One of room.
Uh,
she's a librarian and Wisconsin in Madison.
And,
uh,
she's pregnant.
Finally,
after all these years,
all they're so happy on the youngest one is in Japan.
She's invented your fan for about 20 years.
Freak.
Well,
you have the very well they say,
Oh,
yeah.
Yeah.
And then Robbins,
her oldest son,
her son had a son and a daughter.
The fun is of work for an oil company.
They have two or three children.
They live,
they live in Dallas.
And there there.
Begin.
Right now,
they're all in tow.
Rental property.
Okay,
lying,
You know,
Right?
It's a good deal.
It's like,
uh,
Hayes's is where the college is A pretty good size college.
So what about 17?
And so Ellis is like,
10 miles.
Oh,
yeah.
And it's perfect,
you know,
and for rentals.
You know,
we want to get out.
Said you didn't want a school system better and all that.
Yeah.
So now they somebody has a house for sale?
Somebody died.
I told you got about four or something.
Yeah.
Deal.
You know,
like a damn nuisance.
I tried that once.
Did you?
Yeah.
Oh,
yeah.
Yeah.
Well,
you know you got renters,
Ugo.
You know how that goes.
Sometimes they pay and you gotta go and click right on
that.
No,
the RV parks on the way to go.
So we have to do is rent out the space they they have to provide everything else.
I'm,
uh guess it's a lot easier.
Yeah.
Well,
in this case,
you have new maintenance stuff.
Yeah,
that And they all run on light bulb without your right.
Stay.
Think.
Does grain.
Yeah,
so they get some of that,
but I think they're doing rolling.
Well,
then.
Her husband is a geologist.
He works for an oil company,
and he's been with him for years.
I don't know any work for them,
but then he has college everywhere.
Okay.
Is Granddad was,
uh,
was the president of the bank and during the during
depression,
until a lot roly properties for nothing.
Shenanigans.
And so they have acreage everywhere.
And I have cows.
He has cows everywhere.
So you're doing all right again.
Yeah.
Uh,
I don't think I don't think they have the oil wells themselves
is in the oil mothers.
Too little doing well.
It's that kind of covers all over.
Yeah,
and they're all doing well.
Nobody's in jail.
Yeah,
nobody's finally for bankruptcy and
you hear a story.
Well,
people who do you have that over?
Yeah,
I guess I'm about covered everything for today.